Marching to the New Wonderland
A Difficult Choice
What are you howling for at midnight?
Let me sleep, won't you?
Wolnie, the goats’ only route includes this intersection.
I’m staying up all night so that I can catch them.
There you are!
You're not going anywhere, little goats.
Oh no, it’s Wolffy!
Speed up, Weslie!
Watch this.
Oh no, it’s a dead end!
Wolffy’s catching up to us!
You have nowhere to run!
You little goats...
What’s going on with Wolffy?
Who cares? Let’s get out of here!
I’m... I’m sorry, Mr. Slowy.
You really can't keep your guards up.
What if Wolffy comes?
We haven't seen Wolffy for days now, though.
Even if he does come, it’s fine.
We’ve already set up traps.
What traps?
Help!
He's fallen in. Let's go see.
What are you doing here?
What in the world happened?
Brother Weslie, my dad came down with something strange and serious.
Mommy has used every idea she has,
but nothing has cured him.
Please help him!
Is this another one of Wolffy’s ploys?
It could be.
Wilie wouldn't lie, though.
Let's go check on Wolffy, then.
Wolffy’s heartbeat is normal,
but it’s accompanied by a loud gurgling sound.
This is odd.
It’s as if it’s his stomach.
Right, how did you know?
See for yourself.
Since he got sick, he hasn’t really eaten much.
He must be very hungry.
I’ll make some porridge for him.
I’m helping, too.
What in the world is he sick with?
Could Wolffy be faking it?
We'll test him.
Maybe he's actually sick.
Look, he’s waking up.
Wolnie?
Why’d you get fat?
Wolnie, why do you kind of smell like mutton?
I was about to bite you just now.
I’m just so sick.
It looks like Wolffy is actually very sick.
Is there a cure, Mr. Slowy?
I think I've seen this illness before.
What is it?
Why are there so many Wolnies?
I’m so dizzy.
Extra sunlight helps you get better.
We’ve found some stuff.
Hopefully, it'll help Wolffy.
What did you make him eat, Paddi?
Hawthorn berries. They help with digestion.
He’s already super hungry.
There’s nothing in his stomach to digest.
Back off, Paddi.
Here, try my dit da jow.
Try my slimming cream.
Wait!
Wolffy seems to be even sicker.
He looks like he’s dying.
Am I dying?
What's on your mind, Weslie?
Well...
I disagree!
I disagree, too!
Wolffy’s an evil wolf.
Why would ever we use the Energy Seed to save him?
Wolffy is indeed evil,
but he has a life, too.
But the Energy Seed is for saving the Big Tree.
Without it, what will we use?
It'd be terrible for Wilie to be fatherless, though.
—Weslie, what do you think?　　—Weslie, it’s your choice.
Let’s ask Mr. Slowy’s opinion.
What in the world has Wolffy come down with?
Guys,
please save my dad!
He's feeling worse and worse.
Please save him!
Wilie?
Daddy!
Daddy, how do you feel now?
I'm okay.
Little goats,
can you help me with one last thing?
What is it?
I have a photo.
Please photoshop me to look more energetic.
Make my eyes bigger,
my nose higher,
and my teeth whiter,
so I look better.
Mr. Wolffy, the photo is finished.
Thank you.
Wilie,
when I'm no longer by your side,
you must stay strong.
You must be a man and protect your mom.
—Wolffy!　—Daddy!
Daddy, you’ll be okay!
Son...
Wolnie...
Let’s take a family portrait.
Are we really going to watch Wilie lose his dad
with our own eyes?
Let’s head to Sirius first.
Okay.
What’s the matter?
Look up ahead.
Come on, let's move the branch.
On it!
Let us go!
It isn’t Wolffy, is it?
It is.
It is I, Wolffy.
So you were faking it, Wolffy!
You’re evil!
Catch goats...
You're not catching any goats in this state, you know.
Wolnie...
I’m useless. My family has never eaten mutton before.
I wanted to use my last strength
to let have one last meal of mutton.
I agree!
Sparky, you...
You agree to be eaten?
What? No!
I’m saying that I agree with using the Energy Seed to save Wolffy.
Yay!
Let’s take Wolffy home first.
Okay.
Only Mr. Slowy is left.
Where is he?
What in the world has Wolffy come down with?
I’m so close.
Who says I’m sick?
Weren't... Weren’t you dying?
I took a nap, and now I feel much more energetic.
Watch this!
I've got it!
Wolffy has altitude hypoxic vertigo.
Altitude hypoxic vertigo?
What kind of illness is that?
Although the Big Tree is only a few meters tall,
our shrinking made it feel as though we climbed several kilometers.
Why is Wolffy the only one who got sick?
If you’re tired, or if you lack rest,
then it's very likely you'll get sick.
Only proper rest
can cure altitude hypoxic vertigo.
Mr. Slowy, you’re incredible!
Give me the Energy Seed!
You're not going anywhere!
Wolffy?
You’re finally awake!
Let go of me, Wolnie!
I’m getting the Seed and catching goats for you!
I don’t want to eat mutton! I just want you to be healthy
and safe and sound!
Daddy!
Lighter! I can’t breathe!
Wolffy!
Daddy!
END